(Penny:)you should be able to pick
whichever hobbit you want.
(Penny:)Wish you wouldn't,
but one problem at a time.
(Leonard:)You make a lot of sense.
(Leonard:)I like this table,
and I'm getting it.
(Penny:)Really? This one?
(Leonard:)That one?
(Leonard:)Damn right I like that one.
(Amy:)-Hey.
-Good news.
(Howard:)Someone in this room
gets to take a ride on a rocket.
(Penny:)Fine.
Can I at least shower first?
(Howard:)No, not that.
(Howard:)Although you already agreed
to it, so no take-backs.
(Bernadette:)What are you talking about?
(Howard:)Sit down.
(Howard:)NASA called.
(Howard:)The telescope mount
I installed on the space station
(Howard:)got damaged, and they want me
to go back up and fix it.
(Raj:)Wow.
(Bernadette:)Well, what did you say?
What do you think I....?
I said yes!
(Howard:)Why do you look surprised?